(Leonard:)Sheldon, have you ever once heard me say
that I don't trust Penny?
(Leonard:)Sheldon? Where did he go?
Ugh. Your yelling must've
freaked him out again.
(Leonard:)Where are you going? You just walk away
in the middle of an argument?
No. I'm gonna find your roommate...
(Penny:)...before he hurts himself
trying to cross the street or something.
(Leonard:)Why didn't you say so?
PENNY: Now I need your permission
for that too?
(Leonard:)I can't read your mind, Penny.
PENNY: Really? Why not?
You're so smart and I'm so dumb!
Raj. Raj. Raj.
RAJESH:
Stop knocking. It's open.
(Raj:)Please tell my parents
that our dark matter research...
...is at a critical juncture. I can't come
for my cousin Sanjay's wedding.
(Mrs Koothrappali:)Ask our son what we're supposed
to say to Mr. and Mrs. Chaudri...
(Mrs Koothrappali:)...whose daughter, Lakshmi, is flying in
for the sole purpose of meeting him.
(Raj:)I didn't ask you to set me up.
(Mrs Koothrappali:)-You should be thanking us.
-Yes, Lakshmi got her stomach stapled.
(Dr Koothrappali:)You have an opportunity
to get in with her...
(Dr Koothrappali:)...before she loses weight
and her self-esteem goes up.